<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SeoulStampApplication</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <!--Namsan-->
    <string name="namsan_kor_name">남산 n서울타워</string>
    <string name="namsan_en_name">n seoul tower</string>
    <string name="namsan_tel">+82 2-3455-9277</string>
    <string name="namsan_kor_location">서울 용산구 남산공원길 105 (우) 04340</string>
    <string name="namsan_en_location">04340  105 Namsangongwon-gil, Yongsan-gu, Seoul, Korea (Yongsan-dong 2-ga, YTN Seoul Tower)</string>
    <string name="namsan_homepage">http://www.nseoultower.co.kr/eng/</string>
    <string name="namsan_kor_info">1967년 TV와 라디오 방송을 수도권에 송출하기 위한 한국 최초의 종합전파탑으로 건립\n전파탑에는 국내 주요 공중파 TV와 FM라디오 송신 안테나 등이 설치되어 있으며, 전국 가청 인구의 48%가 N서울타워 전파탑을 통하여 방송을 시청하고 있음\n1980년 일반인에게 공개된 이후 남산의 살아있는 자연과 함께 시민의 휴식공간이자 외국인의 관광 명소로 자리잡음\n최신 LED 조명으로 시시각각 색과 패턴이 변하는 ‘빛의 예술’과의 어우러짐 속에서 다양한 미디어아트를 경험할 수 있음.\n\n남산의 새롭다(new) 의 뜻을 지닌 알파벳 N을 합성한 이름\n한국 최초의 타워형태 관광명소로 약 480m에서 서울을 한눈에 내려다볼 수 있음.\n2005년 낙후된 시설을 리모델링해 산뜻하고 화려한 모습으로 탈바꿈하였으며 장애인차량 전용도로가 있어 전망대까지의 진입이 수월함.\n계절, 이벤트 내용에 따라 서울타워 외관의 색상과 패턴이 변화하는 조명시스템을 도입하여 매일 밤 7시부터 12시까지 ‘서울의 꽃’이라는 주제로 6개의 서치라이트가 다양한 각도로 하늘에 발사되어 꽃이 활짝 핀 모양을 연출함.\n원기둥 형태의 5층을 된 타워룸은 2～3층 전망대와 5층의 회전 전망 레스토랑이 압권을 이루며 사방이 열려있는 원형식당은 360도 회전해 앉은 자리에서 자연스럽게 서울의 사방을 조망할 수 있음</string>
    <string name="namsan_en_info">Namsan Seoul Tower was built in 1969 as Koreas first integrated transmission tower beaming television and radio broadcasts across the capital. Since opening to the public in 1980, it has become a much-loved Seoul landmark. The towers main attractions include multi-colored digital art projected onto the tower at night, a digital observatory, a roof terrace, the HanCook restaurant, the n.Grill restaurant, and the Haneul (Sky) Restroom. Namsan Seoul Towers mountain surroundings on Namsan Mountain have made it a popular place to unwind for locals and tourists alike.\n\nSeoul has a number of viewing platforms where visitors can enjoy the nighttime cityscape or gaze out onto the Hangang (River) but the towers Digital Observatory is unique, offering an astonishing 360 degree panorama over the city, and 32 LCD screens recounting the 600-year history of Seoul. That is why the observatory is so popular and such a source of pride.\n\nSituated on top of the N Plaza, the Roof Terrace is a spacious wooden viewing deck whose exotic atmosphere makes it very popular with lovers. A recent attraction for courting couples is "Locks of Love," thousands of padlocks attached to the fence by romantic Seoulites symbolizing their undying affection.</string>
    <string name="namsan_kor_oprationtime">일-금 오전 10:00 - 오후 11:00\n토     오전 10:00 - 오전 00:00</string>
    <string name="namsan_en_oprationtime">SUN-FRI 10:00 AM - 11:00 PM\nSAT       10:00 AM - 00:00 AM</string>
    <string name="namsan_map_url">https://www.google.com/maps/place/N+Seoul+Tower/@37.5511736,126.9860379,17z/data=!3m1!4b1!4m5!3m4!1s0x357ca257a88e6aa9:0x5cf8577c2e7982a5!8m2!3d37.5511694!4d126.9882266?hl=en</string>

    <!--CHEONGGYECHEON-->
    <string name="cheonggyecheon_kor_name">청계천</string>
    <string name="cheonggyecheon_en_name">Cheonggyecheon</string>
    <string name="cheonggyecheon_tel">+82-2-729-9474</string>
    <string name="cheonggyecheon_kor_location">서울특별시 중구 다동 청계천로 40</string>
    <string name="cheonggyecheon_en_location">40 Cheonggyecheon-ro, Jung-gu, Seoul </string>
    <string name="cheonggyecheon_homepage">https://korean.visitseoul.net/attractions/%EC%B2%AD%EA%B3%84%EC%B2%9C_/34</string>
    <string name="cheonggyecheon_kor_info">청계천이 시작되는 세종로에 조성된 청계광장.청계천 복원 시작지점인 동아일보사 앞에서부터 신답철교 사이로 연장160m, 폭50m, 총 면적 2천 106평의 규모로 조성되었다. 분수와 폭포, 청계천 미니어처, 산책로와 탐방로 등으로 꾸며져있고, 청계천 복원의 의미와 함께 만남과 화합, 평화와 통일을 염원하는 장소로 만들어져 있다. 이 중 광장은 청계천 복원 시작지점중심에 741평 규모로 조성되었고, 우리나라 전통적보자기형태의 디자인을 가져와 다양한 색상의 석재포장으로 우아한 전통미를 살린다. 이 곳에는 청계천 축소모형인 청계 미니어처가 설치되어 복원된 청계천의 모습을 한눈에 볼 수 있다. 청계천을 가로지르는 22개 다리에 대한 해설판도 설치되어 있고, 이외에도 다양한 형상의 분수가 만들어져 아름다운 경관을 연출한다.한편, 광장에서 청계천으로 진입하기 위한 시설로는 왼편에 계단형 진입로, 오른편에 청계탐방로가 들어 서 있다. 청계 탐방로 중 18m 구간에는 터널이 설치돼 광장에서 청계천으로 들어 오는 시민들에게 색다른 경험을 선사한다. 서울시는 청계천광장 조성 후 공휴일에는 이 곳을 차 없는 거리로 만들어 광장, 수변공간, 도로가 시민들의 휴식과 문화공간으로 이용되도록 마련해놓았다. 삼색 조명이 어우러진 캔들 분수와 4m 아래로 떨어지는 2단 폭포가 장관을 연출한다. 폭포 양 옆에는 전국에서 돌을 가져온 8도석으로 제작된 "팔석담"을 깔았다. 밤이면 빛과 물이 어우러지는 환상적인 모습을 연출한다. 또, 청계천 전구간을 1/100로 축소한 미니어쳐 역시 멋진 볼거리를 제공한다.</string>
    <string name="cheonggyecheon_en_info">Cheonggyecheon is an 11 km long modern stream that runs through downtown Seoul. Created as part of an urban renewal project, Cheonggyecheon is a restoration of the stream that was once there before during the Joseon Dynasty (1392-1910). The stream was covered with an elevated highway after the Korean War (1950-1953), as part of the countrys post-war economic development. Then in 2003, the elevated highway was removed to restore the stream to its present form today. The stream starts from Cheonggye Plaza, a popular cultural arts venue, and passes under a total of 22 bridges before flowing into the Hangang (River), with many attractions along its length.Cheonggyecheons turbulent history is on display at the Cheonggyecheon Museum which opened in September 2005. The museum offers visitors the chance to learn about the many changes the stream has seen, including being buried underground and being restored. The story is told with the help of a scale-model and period photographs. Admission is free.</string>
    <string name="cheonggyecheon_kor_oprationtime">월-일 오전 9:00 ~ 오후 8:00</string>
    <string name="cheonggyecheon_en_oprationtime">MON- SUN 9:00 AM ~ 8:00 PM</string>
    <string name="cheonggyecheon_map_url">https://www.google.com/maps/place/37+Mugyo-ro,+Seorin-dong,+Jongno-gu,+Seoul/@37.5693755,126.9768996,17z/data=!3m1!4b1!4m5!3m4!1s0x357ca2ec42fcef39:0x43a3fa4e7eaa35bb!8m2!3d37.5693713!4d126.9790883?hl=en</string>

    <!--HANOK-->
    <string name="hanok_kor_name">남산골 한옥 마을</string>
    <string name="hanok_en_name">Namsangol Hanok Village</string>
    <string name="hanok_tel">+82 2-2264-4412</string>
    <string name="hanok_kor_location">서울 중구 퇴계로34길 28 (우) 046261</string>
    <string name="hanok_en_location">04626  28 Toegye-ro 34-gil, Jung-gu, Seoul</string>
    <string name="hanok_homepage">https://www.hanokmaeul.or.kr/</string>
    <string name="hanok_kor_info">1998년 조성된 남산골한옥마을은 남산 북측 옛 수도방위사령부 부지 총 79,934m²(24,180평)에 한옥 5동, 전통공예관, 천우각, 전통정원, 서울남산국악당, 새천년타임캡슐 광장으로 구성되어 시민과 관광객을 맞이하고 있습니다. 번화한 도심 한 가운데에서 한국 전통문화를 소재로 한 다양한 체험거리를 만나볼 수 있으며, 남산 자락을 따라 전통조경 양식으로 조성된 계곡과 정자, 각종 화초가 만들어내는 아름다운 풍경을 만날 수 있습니다. 전통정원 가장 높은 곳에는 서울정도 600년을 기념하고 400년 후 서울정도 천년을 기대하며 1994년 당대의 기억을 매설한 서울천년타입캡슐 광장이 조성되어 있습니다. 옛 가옥을 복원해 놓은 남산골한옥마을 남산골한옥마을 안으로 들어서면 연못 청학지와 그 곁으로 천우각이 있습니다. 천우각 광장을 지나 돌계단을 오르면 서울 곳곳에 있던 한옥이 이전·복원되어 옛 사람들의 생활방식을 볼 수 있게 한 예스러운 공간이 나타납니다.\n모두 다섯 채의 한옥으로서 삼각동 도편수 이승업 가옥, 삼청동 오위장 김춘영 가옥, 관훈동 민씨 가옥, 제기동 해풍부원군 윤택영 재실, 옥인동 윤씨 가옥이 있습니다. 이 중 건물 이전이 불가능할 정도로 낡은 옥인동 윤씨 가옥만 새 자재를 사용해 복원했고 나머지 건물\n은 종래의 집 부재를 그대로 이전했습니다. 남산골한옥마을에서 즐기는 다양한 체험거리 남산골한옥마을에는 다양한 체험거리가 마련되어 있습니다. 한옥 다섯 채를 활용하여 한옥실내 공간을 체험하면서 동시에 한국 전통문화프로그램을 접할 수 있습니다. 한복 입기, 한지 접기, 한글 쓰기, 전통차 마시기를 체험할 수 있고, 전통예절학교와 한방체험도 운영하고 있습니다. 토요일과 일요일 양일에는 전통혼례가 실제로 치러지고 전통혼례체험도 운영하고 있습니다. 그 밖에도 천우각 맞은편 원두막에서는 짚공예 시연이 이루어지고 있으며, 천우각 무대에서는 태권도 시범공연과 체험 행사에 참여할 수 있습니다. 피금정 마당에서는 제기차기, 윷놀이, 비석치기 등과 같은 민속놀이를 즐길 수 있어 가족이 함께 즐거운 시간을 보낼 수 있습니다. 또한 남산골한옥마을 곳곳을 동행하며 설명해주는 전통문화유산해설사가 상주해 있어 도움을 받을 수도 있습니다.</string>
    <string name="hanok_en_info">Namsangol Hanok Village is a collection of five hanok (traditional Korean houses) from the Joseon Dynasty (1392-1910), recovered from different parts of the city and relocated to the northern foot of Namsan Mountain. The interiors of each of these five houses reflect owners from different walks of life, from the middle class to  high government officials, noblemen and aristocrats.\n\nAt Namsangol Hanok Village, visitors can see the hanok of important figures from the Joseon era including the house of Queen Yuns parents, who was the Queen Consort to King Sunjong, the 27th king of the Joseon Dynasty; the jaesil (study) of Yun Taekyeong, King Sunjongs father-in-law; the house of Min Yeong-hui, a relative of Empress Myeongseong; the house of Lee Seungeop, who was in charge of constructing Gyeongbokgung Palace and the house of Kim Chunyeong, a military official of the Joseon Dynasty.\n\nAt the hanok village, international visitors can participate in traditional Korean activities such as archery and enjoy traditional Korean performances as well. Anyone who is curious about Korean wedding culture should visit the village on the weekend when traditional wedding ceremonies take place.</string>
    <string name="hanok_kor_oprationtime">월 휴일\n화-일 오전 9:00 - 오후 9:00</string>
    <string name="hanok_en_oprationtime">MON closed\nTUE-SUN 9:00 AM - 9:00 PM</string>
    <string name="hanok_map_url">https://www.google.com/maps/place/Namsangol+Hanok+Village/@37.5593192,126.9922883,17z/data=!3m1!4b1!4m5!3m4!1s0x357ca2fcfa6a299b:0x79c3be57e1edbdfe!8m2!3d37.559315!4d126.994477?hl=en</string>

    <!--HANGANG-->
    <string name="hangang_kor_name">한강</string>
    <string name="hangang_en_name">hangang river</string>
    <string name="hangang_tel">+82 2-3780-0561</string>
    <string name="hangang_kor_location">서울특별시 영등포구 여의동 85-6</string>
    <string name="hangang_en_location">07337  280 Yeouidong-ro, Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul</string>
    <string name="hangang_homepage">http://hangang.seoul.go.kr/archives/46758</string>
    <string name="hangang_kor_info">한국의 중부, 강원도·충청북도·경기도·서울특별시를 거쳐 황해로 유입하는 강. 한강은 반만년 유구한 역사를 우리 민족과 더불어 기쁨과 슬픔을 함께 해 온 우리 삶의 터전이며, 서울시민의 가장 대표적인 휴식공원이다.\n한강의 본류인 남한강은 강원도 태백시 창죽동 검용소에서 발원한 하천으로서 삼척시 하장면 부근에서 골지천의 이름으로 북류하다가 광동댐을 지나 석병산(1,010m)에서 발원한 임계천과 합류해 서류, 정선군 북면 여량리에서 황병산(1,407m)을 발원지로 한 송천과 만나 조양강이 되어 흐르다가, 오대천과 합류한 후 남류하여 동강이 된다. 동강은 영월읍에서 평창강과 주천강이 합류해 만들어진 서강과 만난 후 흐르다가 충주시에서 달천, 강원도 원주시와 경기도 여주시 부근에서 섬강·청미천과 만난 후 양화천·복하천·흑천 등의 지류를 합친 후 양수리에서 북한강과 만난다.</string>
    <string name="hangang_en_info">The Hangang River is the most important physical landmark in the city, dividing the north and south. Lined with parks and recreational facilities on both banks, it’s the perfect place to rent bikes, go on cruise up the river, enjoy bird-watching, or splash around and cool off in public swimming pools during the summer months.</string>
    <string name="hangang_kor_oprationtime">월-일 오전 11:00 ~ 오후 9:00</string>
    <string name="hangang_en_oprationtime">MON- SUN 11:00 AM ~ 9:00 PM</string>
    <string name="hangang_map_url">https://www.google.com/maps/place/Eland+Cruise+Terminal/@37.5257853,126.9363057,17z/data=!3m1!4b1!4m5!3m4!1s0x357c9f49026a9a6b:0x4ad2b5bc52380f13!8m2!3d37.5257811!4d126.9384944?hl=en</string>

    <!--COEX-->
    <string name="coex_kor_name">sm타운 코엑스아티움</string>
    <string name="coex_en_name">smtown@coexartium</string>
    <string name="coex_tel">+82 2-1670-6330</string>
    <string name="coex_kor_location">서울 강남구 영동대로 513 (우) 06164</string>
    <string name="coex_en_location">06164  513, Yeongdong-daero, Gangnam-gu, Seoul, Korea SMTOWN@coexartrium </string>
    <string name="coex_homepage">https://www.smtownland.com/index.php</string>
    <string name="coex_kor_info">한류 스타 탄생의 요람\n\n한류의 중심, SM타운에서 아티스트 체험을 해 본다. 스튜디오 견학, 홀로그램 씨어터, 스타일 샵 등 궁금했던 스타 탄생 과정을 가까이서 살펴본다. 견학 내내 좋아하는 한류스타와 마주칠까 설레고, 전문적인 스탭이 스튜디오에서 촬영해준 사진은 훌륭한 인증 사진이 될 것이다.\n\n케이팝 열풍에 맞춘 SMTOWN 코엑스아티움은 열성 팬들에게 훈련실과 녹음실을 투어하고, 홀로그램 공연을 관람하고, 인기 아이돌의 제품과 기념품을 구매할 수 있는 기회를 선사합니다.</string>
    <string name="coex_en_info">If you are a K-pop fan, it is impossible not to know SM Entertainment’s culture complex space, SMTOWN at Coex Artium. The venue has become more popular after the opening of the SMTOWN Museum and SMTOWN External Media, an ultra-high resolution sign that was installed in May 2018.\n\nSMTOWN Museum, located on the third floor, is the first venue where the stories related to the birth and growth of SM Entertainment’s artists are displayed. The museum includes various exhibitions, including SM ARCHIVE, SPECIAL EXHIBITION, and ARTIST GALLERY, all of which are related to music albums, stage photos, outfits and accessories, and behind the scenes stories.\n\nIn addition, the venue offers unique experiences and excitement, such as the SM content-creating tour, where imaginary meetings with SM artists utilizing augmented reality or virtual reality take place.\n\nMeanwhile, SMTOWN External Media is the biggest display in Korea, with a size of four basketball courts. This is why it is also called the Times Square of Korea. K-pop music videos along with the real-time multi live broadcasting channel, “!tLive,” are aired on the screen.\n\nThe biggest hologram theater in Korea is on the fifth and sixth floors, which showcases mostly SM artists’ concert videos. Furthermore, sometimes guests can watch concerts that have not been released on DVD yet. Please check the schedule for further details!\n\nTo top it all off, there is a gift shop (2F) with memorabilia that artists actually wore or picked, a café, and a market (4F) where products with SM artists’ images are sold.</string>
    <string name="coex_kor_oprationtime">월-일 오전 11:30 - 오후 8:30</string>
    <string name="coex_en_oprationtime">MON-SUN 11:30 AM - 8:30 PM</string>
    <string name="coex_map_url">https://www.google.com/maps/place/SM+Town+Coex+Artium/@37.5099894,127.0592203,17z/data=!3m1!4b1!4m5!3m4!1s0x357ca44027a18801:0x5ecf94d0dc43af63!8m2!3d37.5099852!4d127.061409?hl=en</string>

    <!--STAR_LOAD-->
    <string name="kstar_kor_name">k 스타로드</string>
    <string name="kstar_en_name">k star road</string>
    <string name="kstar_tel">+82-2-3445-0111</string>
    <string name="kstar_kor_location">서울 강남구 영동대로 513 (우) 06164</string>
    <string name="kstar_en_location">407, Apgujeong-ro, Gangnam-gu, Seoul, Republic of Korea</string>
    <string name="kstar_homepage">https://korean.visitseoul.net/Hallyu/K-star-ROAD-%EA%B0%95%EB%82%A8-%ED%95%9C%EB%A5%98%EC%8A%A4%ED%83%80%EA%B1%B0%EB%A6%AC_/15768</string>
    <string name="kstar_kor_info">케이팝(K-POP) 중심의 한류문화를 체험하고 이른바 ‘강남스타일’의 쇼핑을 즐기고 싶다면 강남 한류스타거리(K-star ROAD)부터 찾아보자. 압구정동 갤러리아백화점에서부터 큐브엔터테인먼트까지 약 1km 가량 이어지는 한류스타거리에는 소녀시대, 엑소, 동방신기 등 아이돌 한류스타들을 상징화한 아트토이(art toy), 일명 ‘강남돌(GangnamDol)’들이 대로변을 장식하고 있다. 가로등이나 횡단보도에 설치된 새를 형상화한 안내판 ‘K버드’의 부리와 발자국을 따라가면 스타들의 단골 맛집과 패션숍을 쉽게 찾을 수 있고, 상점 옆 무인정보단말기를 통해 스타들의 다양한 정보도 얻을 수 있다. 스타들이 다녔던 중고등학교와 실제로 살았었던 집, 스타들의 단골 분식집과 만화방처럼 그들의 이야기가 담긴 명소들도 강남 한류스타거리 곳곳에 보물처럼 자리하고 있다. 강남의 트렌디한 카페들과 유명 백화점, 고급 쇼핑매장에서 즐기는 쇼핑도 잊지 말자.\n\nSM, JYP, CUBE 등 연예기획사가 밀집한 압구정동과 청담동 일대는 이전부터 한류 팬들의 발길이 끊이지 않는 관광객들의 순례지였다. 팬들이 스타를 직접 만나고, 스타들의 스토리를 따라가며 깊은 소통을 할 수 있도록, 강남 한류스타거리는 스타들의 단골 가게나 사연이 담긴 특별한 장소들을 끊임없이 개발하며 흥미로운 여행지로 거듭나고 있다.</string>
    <string name="kstar_en_info">If you would like to experience the Hallyu culture of K-POP and enjoy Gangnam Style shopping, visit the K-star Road. On the K-star Road led for 1 km from Apgujeong-dong Galleria Department Store to Cube Entertainment, art toys symbolizing Hallyu stars including Girls Generation, EXO and TVXQ, the GangnamDols are decorating the road. When you follow the beak and the footsteps of ‘K Bird’ installed on lampposts and crosswalks, you can find celebrities’ favorite restaurants and fashion stops, and gain information of celebrities through the information displayer next to the store. The middle and high schools of celebrities, the homes that they had actually lived in, their favorite snack stores and comic shops are located here and there in the K-star Road. Do not forget the trendy cafes of Gangnam, famous department stores, and shopping in the high-end shopping stores.\n\nApgujeong-dong and Cheongdam-dong with entertainment corporations SM, JYP and CUBE concentrated have been the must-see spots of Hallyu fans. For the fans to actually meet the stars, to follow the stories of stars, the Gangnam Hallyu K-star Road is becoming an interesting traveling spot by developing the special places with the stores of celebrities</string>
    <string name="kstar_kor_oprationtime">월-일 오전 10:00 - 오후 7:00\n쉬는시간 오후 1:00 - 오후 2:00</string>
    <string name="kstar_en_oprationtime">MON-SUN 10:00 AM - 7:00 PM\nBreak 1:00 PM ~ 2:00 PM</string>
    <string name="kstar_map_url">https://www.google.com/maps/place/Gangnam+K-Star+Road+(%EA%B0%95%EB%82%A8+%EC%BC%80%EC%9D%B4%EC%8A%A4%ED%83%80+%EB%A1%9C%EB%93%9C)/@37.5278751,127.0396184,17z/data=!3m1!4b1!4m5!3m4!1s0x357ca5a0313b76bd:0x8d871c80a66e3267!8m2!3d37.5278751!4d127.0418071?hl=en</string>

    <!--LOTTE_TOWER-->
    <string name="lotte_kor_name">롯데월드타워 롯대월드몰</string>
    <string name="lotte_en_name">Lotte World Mall</string>
    <string name="lotte_tel">+82 2-3213-5000</string>
    <string name="lotte_kor_location">서울 송파구 올림픽로 300 롯데월드</string>
    <string name="lotte_en_location">05551  300, Olympic-ro, Songpa-gu, Seoul, Korea (Shincheon-dong 29)</string>
    <string name="lotte_homepage">https://www.lwt.co.kr/tower/ko/main/main.do</string>
    <string name="lotte_kor_info">한국적 곡선의 미를 지닌 한국 전통의 도자기와 붓의 형상을 모티브로 설계된 롯데월드타워는 총 123층, 555M 높이로 세계 5위의 초고층 빌딩이다. 대지면적은 축구장의 12.2배, 전체 총 면적은 축구장의 110배에 달하는 거대한 수직도시이다. 2016년 12월 마침내 준공되었으며, 특급 호텔 "시그니엘 서울"과, 화려한 서울의 야경을 볼 수 있는 전망대인 "서울스카이", 최고급 레지던스와 오피스 공간, 복합기능공간 등으로 구성되어있다. 롯데월드몰은 국내 최대의 명품 백화점인 "에비뉴엘"과 국내 시내 면세점 중 최대 면적을 자랑하는 "롯데면세점", "롯데 하이마트", "쇼핑몰", "롯데마트" 등이 위치해있는 쇼핑 관광의 명소로 다양한 국내외 브랜드를 만날 수 이는 공간이다. 쇼핑공간 외에도 문화·예술공간으로 아시아 최대규모의 멀티플렉스인 "롯데시네마 월드타워관", "롯데월드 아쿠아리움", 국내 최초 빈야드 스타일의 "롯데 콘서트홀"이 있어 쇼핑과 엔터테인먼트를 함께 즐길 수 있는 복합 쇼핑몰이다.</string>
    <string name="lotte_en_info">Lotte World Mall where you could meet the latest trend fashion and high-end lifestyle is a shopping zone with Lotte Avenuel, South Korea’s largest luxury department store. Entertainment experiences including the premium shopping zones of foreign brands, the largest aquarium in city, movie theatres, Lotte Mart, Hi Mart, Hallyu contents mall Star Avenue, beauty shops, spa and cultural and entertainment experiences are provided. Including seafood buffets, restaurants, food courts, it includes various facilities including baby carriage rentals, children’s resting room, medical office, and clothing repair rooms.\nLotte world Tower, a high-rise building with 123 floors, height of 555m, the 6th tallest building in the world is future-oriented building with 6-star hotel and the largest observatory in the world, and is rising as the landmark of Seoul, and a world-famous tourist spot.\n\nThe food theme of Lotte World Tower enacts the Jong-no streets of the 1930s, and the Myungdong streets of 1968-80s, and is receiving attention as the shooting scenes of various dramas and movies. In the examination episode of the Mudo Singing Festival of Infinite Challenge, the Lotte World Mall Cine Park appeared, and the scenes where the actor Kim Soo Hyun removes the shell of the lobster to Kong Hyo Jin in the drama The Producers, and where the beautiful couple Kong Seung Yeon and Lee Jong Hyun share fish-shaped bread while playing games in the variety show We Got Married were filmed at Lotte World. It provides various services of concierge desk including interpretation guidance for foreign tourists, storage of goods, and recharging smartphones, foreign currency exchange desk, foreigner desk and tax refunds that you can enjoy convenient shopping here.</string>
    <string name="lotte_kor_oprationtime">월-일 오전 9:30 - 오후 11:00</string>
    <string name="lotte_en_oprationtime">MON-SUN 9:30 AM -117:00 PM</string>
    <string name="lotte_map_url">https://www.google.com/maps/place/37+Mugyo-ro,+Seorin-dong,+Jongno-gu,+Seoul/@37.5693755,126.9768996,17z/data=!3m1!4b1!4m5!3m4!1s0x357ca2ec42fcef39:0x43a3fa4e7eaa35bb!8m2!3d37.5693713!4d126.9790883?hl=enna</string>

    <!--BANPO_BRIDGE-->
    <string name="banpo_kor_name">세빛섬</string>
    <string name="banpo_en_name">some sevit</string>
    <string name="banpo_tel">+82-2-3477-58094</string>
    <string name="banpo_kor_location">서울특별시 반포2동</string>
    <string name="banpo_en_location">06500  683, Olympic-daero, Seocho-gu, Seoul, Korea (Banpo-dong)</string>
    <string name="banpo_kor_info">‘한강을 아름답게 밝혀주는 세 개의 빛나는 섬’이란 의미를 지닌 세빛섬은 세계 최초의 수상 문화공간이다. 가빛섬, 채빛섬, 솔빛섬, 예빛섬 등 총 4개의 인공섬으로 이뤄져 있으며, 웨딩 컨벤션을 비롯해 이탈리안 레스토랑, 뷔페, 카페가 마련되어 있고, 각종 전시·공연·이벤트가 이뤄지는 공간으로 활용되고 있다. 서울의 야간명소로도 손꼽히는 세빛섬은 화려하고 아름다운 LED 조명이 한강과 어우러지는 환상적인 야경을 자랑하며, 각종 드라마와 영화촬영지로 각광받고 있다. 한강 위에서 즐기는 맛있는 식사와 문화체험과 함께 FIC 컨벤션, 야외데크, 옥상 전망대 등 10개의 포토스팟에서 멋진 사진을 남기는 것도 잊지 말자.\n\n한강의 매력을 제대로 느낄 수 있는 세빛섬은 대표적인 서울 야간명소이자, 각종 영화, 드라마 촬영지로 인기를 얻고 있다. 신 한류스타 박서준과 슈퍼주니어의 최시원이 등장한 드라마 그녀는 예뻤다, 배우 정우성이 열연한 드라마 아테나가 이곳에서 촬영됐다. 특히, 세계적인 블록버스터 영화 어벤져스>에서 유전자연구소로 등장, 세빛섬은 이색 관광지로 유명세를 탔고, 지금도 국내외 많은 관광객들이 방문하고 있다.</string>
    <string name="banpo_en_info">Some Sevit, with the meaning ‘three shining islands brightening the Han River’ is the world’s first floating cultural space. It is made with four artificial islands including Some Gavi, Some Chaevit, Some Solvit and Some Yevit, with wedding halls, Italian restaurants, buffets and cafes, and is being utilized as a space for various exhibitions, performances and events. The Some Sevit known to be a popular night scene of South Korea has colorful and beautiful LED lights with Han River, receiving attention as shooting scenes of various dramas and movies. Enjoy delicious meals and cultural experiences, and remember to take amazing photos at the 10 photo spots of FIC Convention, outdoor deck and the roof observatory.\n\nSome Sevit where you could feel the charm of the Han River is gaining popularity as one of the places where you could enjoy Seoul’s night scenery, and filming spots for various movies and dramas. The drama She Was Pretty> featuring the new Hallyu star Park Seo Joon, and Athene featuring actor Jung Woo Seong were filmed here. Especially, it was featured as a gene laboratory in the blockbuster movie , making Some Sevit an exotic tourism spot, and numerous tourists are visiting from South Korea and abroad.</string>
    <string name="banpo_homepage">http://www.somesevit.co.kr/kr/index.do</string>
    <string name="banpo_kor_oprationtime">월-일 오전 11:00 ~ 오후 10:00</string>
    <string name="banpo_en_oprationtime">MON- SUN 11:00 AM ~ 10:00 PM</string>
    <string name="banpo_map_url">https://www.google.com/maps/place/SEBITSEOM+Seoul+Floating+Island/@37.5118143,126.9928289,17z/data=!3m1!4b1!4m5!3m4!1s0x357ca1802c333b2f:0x80da7a424e905385!8m2!3d37.5118101!4d126.9950176?hl=en</string>

    <!--GYEONBOK-->
    <string name="gyungbok_kor_name">경복궁</string>
    <string name="gyungbok_en_name">Gyeongbokgung Palace</string>
    <string name="gyungbok_tel">+82 2-3700-3900</string>
    <string name="gyungbok_kor_location">서울 종로구 사직로 161</string>
    <string name="gyungbok_en_location">161 Sajik-ro, Sejongno, Jongno-gu, Seoul</string>
    <string name="gyungbok_homepage">http://www.royalpalace.go.kr:8080/html/eng/main/main.jsp</string>
    <string name="gyungbok_kor_info">경복궁은 1395년 태조 이성계에 의해서 새로운 조선왕조의 법궁으로 지어졌다. 경복궁은 동궐(창덕궁)이나 서궐(경희궁)에 비해 위치가 북쪽에 있어 "북궐"이라 불리기도 했다. 경복궁(사적 제117호)은 5대 궁궐 가운데 으뜸의 규모와 건축미를 자랑한다. 경복궁 근정전에서 즉위식을 가진 왕들을 보면 제2대 정종, 제4대 세종, 제6대 단종, 제7대 세조, 제9대 성종, 제11대 중종, 제13대 명종 등이다. 경복궁은 임진왜란 때 상당수의 건물이 불타 없어진 아픔을 갖고 있으며, 고종 때에 흥선대원군의 주도 아래 7,700여칸에 이르는 건물들을 다시 세웠다. 그러나 또 다시 명성황후 시해사건이 일어나면서 왕조의 몰락과 함께 경복궁도 왕궁으로서의 기능을 상실하고 말았다. 경복궁에는 조선시대의 대표적인 건축물인 경회루와 향원정의 연못이 원형대로 남아 있으며, 근정전의 월대와 조각상들은 당시의 조각미술을 대표한다. 현재 흥례문 밖 서편에는 국립고궁 박물관이 위치하고 있고, 경복궁 내 향원정의 동편에는 국립민속 박물관이 위치하고 있다.</string>
    <string name="gyungbok_en_info">Gyeongbokgung Palace was the first and largest of the royal palaces built during the Joseon Dynasty. Built in 1395, Gyeongbokgung Palace was located at the heart of newly appointed capital of Seoul (then known as Hanyang) and represented the sovereignty of the Joseon Dynasty. The largest of the Five Grand Palaces (the others being Gyeonghuigung Palace, Deoksugung Palace, Changgyeonggung Palace, Changdeokgung Palace), Gyeongbokgung served as the main palace of the Joseon Dynasty.\n\nThe Korean government has invested much time and effort into rebuilding, restoring, and maintaining the palace for future generations. These efforts include work to rebuild and restore the buildings that were destroyed during the Japanese occupation. Visitors to Gyeongbokgung can also visit the National Palace Museum of Korea and the National Folk Museum of Korea as they are located on the palace grounds.\n\nTo increase ease of accessibility from Gyeongbokgung Palace to Seochon and vice versa, the palaces western gate, Yeongchumun, was opened to the public on December 2018. For the past 43 years, there were only 3 entrances to Gyeongbokgung Palace - the southern gate Gwanghwamun, the northern gate Sinmumun, and the eastern entrance of National folk Museum of Korea. However, with the opening of the western gate Yeongchumun, entry to the palace from all directions has been now made possible.</string>
    <string name="gyungbok_kor_oprationtime">화 휴일\n수-월 오전 9:00 - 오후 5:00</string>
    <string name="gyungbok_en_oprationtime">Tuesday closed\nWED-MON 9:00 AM - 5:00 PM</string>
    <string name="gyungbok_map_url">https://www.google.com/maps/place/Gyeongbokgung+Palace/@37.5796212,126.9748523,17z/data=!3m1!4b1!4m5!3m4!1s0x357ca2c74aeddea1:0x8b3046532cc715f6!8m2!3d37.579617!4d126.977041?hl=en</string>

    <!--DUKSOO-->
    <string name="duksoo_kor_name">덕수궁</string>
    <string name="duksoo_en_name">Duksoo Place</string>
    <string name="duksoo_tel">+82 2-771-9951</string>
    <string name="duksoo_kor_location">서울 중구 세종대로 99 (우) 04519</string>
    <string name="duksoo_en_location">99 Sejong-daero, Jeong-dong, Jung-gu, Seoul</string>
    <string name="duksoo_homepage">http://www.deoksugung.go.kr/</string>
    <string name="duksoo_kor_info">사적 제124호의 덕수궁은 본디 왕궁이 아니었다. 원래 성종의 형인 월산대군(1454∼1488)의 집이었으나, 1592년 임진왜란 때 왕궁이 모두 불타서 1593년 행궁으로 사용하기 시작하였다. 선조임금은 의주로 피난갔다가 한양으로 환도한 뒤 덕수궁에서 머무른다. 선조의 뒤를 이은 광해군은 1608년 이곳 행궁에서 즉위한 후 1611년 행궁을 경운궁이라 고쳐부르고 7년동안 왕궁으로 사용하다가 1615년에 창덕궁으로 옮기면서 이곳에는 선왕인 선조의 계비인 인목 대비만을 유폐시켰다. 1618년에는 인목대비의 존호를 폐지하고, 경운궁을 서궁이라 낮추어 부르기도 하였다. 1623년 인조반정으로 광해군이 폐위되고 인조가 이곳 즉조당에서 즉의하고 창덕궁으로 옮긴 이후 270년 동안은 별궁으로 사용되었다. 1897년 고종황제가 러시아 공관에 있다가 환궁하면서 이곳을 다시 왕궁으로 사용하게 되었는데, 그때부터 다시 경운궁이라 부르게 되었고 그 규모도 다시 넓혔다. 그리고 고종 황제는 1907년 순종에게 양위한 후, 왕궁을 창덕궁으로 옮긴 후에도 이곳에 거처하였는데, 이때부터 고종 황제의 장수를 비는 뜻에서 덕수궁이라 부르게 되었다. 이런 까닭에 요즘와서는 경운궁이라는 본래의 명칭을 사용해야 한다는 주장도 제기되고 있다.덕수궁에서 지난 날 많은 건물이 있었으나 현재 18,635평의 경내에 남아 있는 것은 대한문,중화전, 광명문, 석어당, 준명당, 즉조당, 함녕전, 덕홍전 및 석조전 등에 불과하다. 덕수궁은 특히 구한말 비운의 황제 고종이 일제의 압박으로 양위를 강요당하고, 한 많은 여생을 보내다가 1919년 1월 22일 덕수궁 함녕전에서 일제에 의해 독살당하여 돌아가신 것으로 알려져 3·1 독립운동의 직접적인 계기가 되었던 곳이다.</string>
    <string name="duksoo_en_info">Deoksugung Palace is unique among Korean palaces in having a modern seal engraving and a western style garden and fountain. Medieval and modern style architecture exists together in harmony in Deoksugung Palace. The Changing of the Royal Guard can be seen in front of Daehanmun (Gate) and is a very popular event for many visitors. During the Joseon Dynasty, the royal guard was responsible for opening and closing the palace gate as well as patrolling around the gate area. Outside the palace is a picturesque road flanked by a stone wall which is much loved by visitors.\n\nOriginally, Deoksugung Palace was not a palace. The Imjin War (the Japanese invasions in 1592) left all the palaces in Korea severely damaged. When King Seonjo (the fourteenth king of the Joseon Dynasty) returned to Seoul from his evacuation, the primary palace Gyeongbokgung Palace had been burnt to the ground and other palaces were also heavily damaged. A temporary palace was chosen from among the houses of the royal family. This is the origin of Deoksugung Palace. King Gwanghaegun (the fifteenth king of the Joseon Dynasty) named the palace Gyeongungung, formalizing it as a royal palace. Since then it has been used as an auxiliary palace by many Joseon kings. In 1897, Emperor Gojong (the twenty-sixth king of the Joseon Dynasty) stayed here and expanded it. The modern buildings such as Seokjojeon (Hall) were constructed during this period. In 1907, the palace was renamed Deoksugung.</string>
    <string name="duksoo_kor_oprationtime">월 휴일\n화-일오전 9:00 - 오후 9:00</string>
    <string name="duksoo_en_oprationtime">MON closed\nTUE-SUN 9:00 AM - 5:00 PM</string>
    <string name="duksoo_map_url">https://www.google.com/maps/place/Deoksugung/@37.5658091,126.9729574,17z/data=!3m1!4b1!4m5!3m4!1s0x357ca28d3199c531:0x7a2d35df0efd2d8!8m2!3d37.5658049!4d126.9751461?hl=en</string>

</resources>
